AHMAD NOVAL FAHMI

+6285156534857 | novalahmad846@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/ahmadnoval12 |

github.com/ahmadnoval | Jakarta Selatan, DKI Jakarta

INTRODUCTION

I am a full-stack web developer who graduated with a degree in information engineering. Experience working on projects through Independent Study in the Kampus Merdeka program, volunteering, and collaborative projects. As an adaptable learner, I have successfully tackled various problem-solving challenges both individually and as part of a team. I am motivated to continue growing and contributing.

EXPERIENCE

PT. Impactbyte Educational Technology | (Independent Study from Kampus Merdeka)

(Feb 2023 - Jun 2023)

Full-stack Web Developer

- Collaborated with the team to design UI/UX design.
- Implement design and create website using ReactJS Vite.
- Design databases and build APIs using NodeJS and Express.js.
- Set up and deploying website using Virtual Machine from Google Cloud Platform.

PT. Nurul Fikri Cipta Inovasi | (Independent Study from Kampus Merdeka)

(Agu 2022 - Dec 2022)

Full-stack Web Developer

- Collaborate project using Github.
- Layouting template website content.
- Implement design and build APIs using Laravel.
- Deploy and hosting website that have been finished into Webmin.

EDUCATION

Sekolah Tinggi Teknologi Terpadu Nurul Fikri - Depok, Indonesia

(2020 - 2024)

Bachelor in Information Engineering (GPA 3.56 / 4.00)

MA Saadatuddarain - Jakarta, Indonesia

Social science (2015 – 2018)

SKILLS

Hard Skill: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, SQL.

Soft Skill: Team Works, Problem Solving, and Time Management.

Software Skill:

- Frameworks & Libraries: NodeJS, ReactJS Vite, Express.js, Laravel.
- Tools: Postman, Figma, GitHub, VSCode.

FEATURED PROJECTS

- Remedial A React web app that offers knowledge about art and literacy through art understanding, discussion about millennial art, and graphic printing practice.
- Livechat A chat that I made myself in my spare time.
- Medilab A health website to buy medicine or check your health with a professional doctor.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Front-End Web Development Skilvul #Tech4Impact (MSIB Batch 4), 30 June 2023
- Full-stack Web Developer Academy NF Computer (MSIB Batch 3), 31 December 2022